gohigheris.com 2013-04-23

# Privacy Policy

##  [ Privacy Policy](https://www.gohigheris.com/policies/privacy-policy)

#### version 2.0  
last updated 2012 January 29

This privacy policy applies to the use of gohigheris.com and affiliated subdomains which are owned and operated by Go Higher Information Services, LLC (Go Higher).  Go Higher offers to its visitors and clients (Visitors) software products, custom coding, Joomla! components, web design, site development, support services and various services to support both end users and professional web companies.  This privacy policy is in place to explain how and why Go Higher collects certain personal information from our Visitors, and what we do with that information.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION & USE

Go Higher is the sole owner of the information collected on gohigheris.com.  Go Higher collects personally identifiable information from our Visitors at several different points of our web site in order to fulfill specific requests for service and/or products that we provide our Visitors.

### WHY WE NEED TO COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information from our Visitors is used to enable Go Higher to deliver products, support, and services to our Visitors. For example, some of our products and services may require some form of registration or subscription. Contact details of our Visitors may also be required from time to time to notify them of site updates or allow them to participate in comments, support forum, reviews, or newsletters.

Some of the information we collect, including that obtained from our online forms or facilities, is used to help Go Higher develop and improve the quality of our products and services, which in turn, provides our Visitors with both a more satisfying and enjoyable online experience.

### USE OF INFORMATION

Visitor’s email addresses and other personal information provided by visitors may be used to enable us to send promotional material (on other products and services) that we consider may be of interest to Visitors. However, Visitors may at any time, notify Go Higher that they do not wish to receive this material via an opt-out facility contained within our newsletters or on our website.   Personal information that Visitors provide to Go Higher may also be shared among our subsidiaries. All subsidiaries are required to keep such information private and confidential and otherwise deal with such personal information strictly in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

Go Higher collects and stores personal information that is voluntarily provided by our Visitors as part of doing business with us. Such information may include Visitor’s full name, addresses (including home, postal and email address) and telephone numbers. We DO NOT collect financial information for a Visitor such as credit card or bank account information.

### PROFILE

Go Higher stores information that is collected through cookies, log files, clear gifs, or third party resources to create a profile of your preferences. This information is tied to your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you.  Go Higher collects this personal information and makes use of these details to provide you with products and services and to better manage the relationship with you and to better support products or services you may be subscribed to.

### WEBSITE ACTIVITY

Go Higher provides services and products through our website. When Visitors view our website, our web servers record anonymous information such as the time and date this website is viewed and the web pages/URL’s requested. This information assists us to improve the structure of our website and monitor their performance.

### COOKIES

Go Higher makes use of cookies on this website. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to a Visitors hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The browser stores the information, and sends the information back to the server each time a Visitor request a webpage from the server. The use of cookies is an industry standard and are used by the majority of Website operators.

By keeping a record of how and when Visitors view our website, cookies help us see which web pages are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to our website are based on such data as the total number of Visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide products and services that are better tailored to our Visitors and Visitors needs.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. Visitors can reset their browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some parts of our website, or the products and services provided through our website, may not function properly or may be considerably slower if you do not enable cookies on your Internet browser.

### IP ADDRESSES

Go Higher web servers register the type of web browsers that Visitors are using and their IP address when Visitors access our website.  Go Higher collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate traffic information to our Visitors, fraud detection and to generally audit the use of our website. When Visitors request pages from our website, our servers may log the Visitor’s IP addresses.  Go Higher does not normally link IP addresses to any personal information, which means that a Visitor’s session will be logged, but the Visitor otherwise remains anonymous, unless in support tickets or forum.  Go Higher can and will make use of IP addresses to identify a Visitor when it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms of service or to protect the integrity of our services and website, as well as to protect our interests and those of our Visitors.

### WHEN WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION

Go Higher takes all reasonable steps to protect the privacy of our Visitors and Visitors and to ensure that the personal information we collect and store is protected against unauthorised disclosure to third parties.  However, there may be times when Go Higher may be required to disclose personal information of a Visitor without their consent. While rare, this may occur when:

  * Compelled by law enforcement to provide such information
  * When we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against the Visitor or another person who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of Go Higher, other Visitors or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.
  * When required by law.

### COMMUNICATIONS FROM SITE

Go Higher will occasionally send you information on products, services or specials that we may be running. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please contact support [at] gohigheris.com to be removed from our list or simply use the opt-out within our website or newsletter.

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. We will also send email on critical updates of our products that you have purchased.   Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please contact support [at] gohigheris.com

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Visitors should be aware that on our website, there are links to third party websites. If you "click" a link contained on one of our sites, the "click" may result in you leaving our site and your browser being redirected to a website owned and controlled by a third party.  In this case, Go Higher recommends that you refer to the privacy statement of the website you visit. Neither Go Higher nor its subsidiaries have any control over and hence, accepts no responsibility for the content of these sites or the actions of the operators in relation to the collection of personal information of users of these sites.  While Go Higher makes every effort to protect your personal information and your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.  Visitors should keep in mind that whenever personal information is given out online, there is a risk that the information can be intercepted and used by third parties without the knowledge of either party.  Go Higher is in no way responsible or liable for the misuse of personal information obtained in this manner.

### ACCESS AND ACCURACY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

If Go Higher holds your personal information, we will, where possible, provide you with reasonable access to the information upon your request.  You may also log in to your account and change this information at any time.

Go Higher will take reasonable steps to correct the information upon being put on notice by the Visitor, so that at all times, it is accurate, complete and up to date.

### YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS

By using this website or our affiliated websites, you signify your assent to the terms and conditions contained herein (as amended from time to time). If you do not agree to be bound by its terms, we request you to close your browsing session and not to use our our website in the future.

More than 2000 members use our products and services on their website!   [Register Now!](https://www.gohigheris.com/component/users/?task=registration)
